const quizData = [
    {
      question: 'Who was the first Sikh Guru?',
      options: ['Guru Nanak', 'Guru Gobind Singh', 'Guru Amar Das', 'Guru Ram Das'],
      answer: 'Guru Nanak',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the last Sikh Guru?',
      options: ['Guru Nanak', 'Guru Gobind Singh', 'Guru Amar Das', 'Guru Har Krishan'],
      answer: 'Guru Gobind Singh',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Guru established the Khalsa?',
      options: ['Guru Nanak', 'Guru Gobind Singh', 'Guru Amar Das', 'Guru Ram Das'],
      answer: 'Guru Gobind Singh',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the fifth Sikh Guru?',
      options: ['Guru Nanak', 'Guru Amar Das', 'Guru Arjan Dev', 'Guru Hargobind'],
      answer: 'Guru Arjan Dev',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Guru compiled the Adi Granth?',
      options: ['Guru Nanak', 'Guru Amar Das', 'Guru Arjan Dev', 'Guru Gobind Singh'],
      answer: 'Guru Arjan Dev',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was known for his teachings on humility and service?',
      options: ['Guru Nanak', 'Guru Amar Das', 'Guru Arjan Dev', 'Guru Har Rai'],
      answer: 'Guru Amar Das',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Guru was the first to establish a central Sikh community?',
      options: ['Guru Nanak', 'Guru Ram Das', 'Guru Amar Das', 'Guru Hargobind'],
      answer: 'Guru Ram Das',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the seventh Sikh Guru?',
      options: ['Guru Nanak', 'Guru Hargobind', 'Guru Har Rai', 'Guru Har Krishan'],
      answer: 'Guru Har Rai',
    },
    {
      question: 'Which Guru is known for his role in expanding Sikhism beyond the Punjab region?',
      options: ['Guru Nanak', 'Guru Amar Das', 'Guru Har Gobind', 'Guru Gobind Singh'],
      answer: 'Guru Gobind Singh',
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the fourth Sikh Guru?',
      options: ['Guru Nanak', 'Guru Ram Das', 'Guru Hargobind', 'Guru Amardas'],
      answer: 'Guru Ram Das',
    },
  ];
  
  export default quizData;
  